(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{2:function(e,t,i){e.exports={Container:"Quiz_Container__1Y6Ji",ProgressBar:"Quiz_ProgressBar__1Gf98",Timer:"Quiz_Timer__nkMKq",Question:"Quiz_Question__XytnN",Hide:"Quiz_Hide__26QlX",Btns:"Quiz_Btns__1zruj",Submit:"Quiz_Submit__Rp1cQ"}},21:function(e,t,i){},23:function(e,t,i){"use strict";i.r(t);var c=i(0),o=i(4),n=i.n(o),s=i(10),a=i(5),r=(i(21),i(3)),l=i(2),h=i.n(l),u=i(1),d=function(e){var t=e.index,i=e.problem,c=e.setUsersChoice,o=e.userChoice;if(!i)return Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"Spinner"});var n=i.question,s=i.choices;return Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:h.a.Question,children:Object(u.jsx)("h3",{children:t+1+". "+n})}),s.map((function(e,i){return Object(u.jsxs)("form",{children:[Object(u.jsx)("input",{id:i,type:"radio",name:"radio"+i,checked:o===i+1,onChange:function(){c(t,i+1)}}),Object(u.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:i,children:Object(u.jsx)("p",{className:h.a.Answers,children:e})})]},i.toString())}))]})},j=i.p+"static/media/back.a98e70f8.svg",b=i.p+"static/media/next.7568cec3.svg",f=function(e){var t=e.time;return Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("p",{className:h.a.ProgressBar,children:0===t?"Time's up !!":t+" seconds left"}),Object(u.jsx)("progress",{max:100,value:100-t,color:"danger"})]})},m=Object(a.b)((function(e){return{questions:e.quiz}}))((function(e){var t=Object(c.useState)(100),i=Object(r.a)(t,2),o=i[0],n=i[1],s=Object(c.useState)(!0),a=Object(r.a)(s,2),l=a[0],m=a[1],p=Object(c.useState)(null),O=Object(r.a)(p,2),g=O[0],x=O[1],v=Object(c.useState)(0),w=Object(r.a)(v,2),_=w[0],q=w[1],y=Object(c.useState)([]),C=Object(r.a)(y,2),N=C[0],S=C[1],W=function(e){m(!1);for(var t=0,i=0;i<g.length;i++)g[i].correct===N[i]&&(t+=10);alert("Congrats! Your score is"+t+" out of 100"),window.location.reload(!1)};return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){0===o&&W(),0!==o&&setTimeout((function(){n(o-1)}),1e3)}),[o]),Object(c.useEffect)((function(){x(function(e){for(var t=e.length-1;t>0;t--){var i=Math.floor(Math.random()*(t+1)),c=e[t];e[t]=e[i],e[i]=c}return e}(e.questions).splice(0,10))}),[]),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:h.a.Container,children:[Object(u.jsx)(f,{time:o}),Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),Object(u.jsx)(d,{index:_,problem:g?g[_]:null,active:l,userChoice:N[_],setUsersChoice:function(e,t){var i=N;i[e]=t,S(i)}}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:h.a.Btns,children:[Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:h.a.Prev,children:0!==_?Object(u.jsx)(u.Fragment,{children:Object(u.jsx)("button",{"data-visible":toString(0!==_),color:"info",onClick:function(e){q(_-1)},children:Object(u.jsx)("img",{src:j,style:{marginLeft:"-4px"},alt:"Prev"})})}):Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:h.a.Hide,children:Object(u.jsx)("img",{src:j,style:{marginLeft:"-4px"},alt:"Prev"})})}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:h.a.Next,children:9!==_?Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("button",{color:"info",onClick:function(e){q(_+1)},children:Object(u.jsx)("img",{src:b,style:{marginRight:"-4px"},alt:"Next"})})," "]}):Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:h.a.Hide,children:Object(u.jsx)("img",{src:b,style:{marginRight:"-4px"},alt:"Next"})})})]}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:h.a.Submit,children:9===_?Object(u.jsx)("button",{color:"info",onClick:function(){W()},children:"SUBMIT"}):" "})]})})),p=i(6),O=i.n(p),g=function(){var e=Object(c.useState)(!1),t=Object(r.a)(e,2),i=t[0],o=t[1];return Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:O.a.App,children:Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:O.a.Container,children:i?Object(u.jsx)(m,{}):Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:O.a.Content,children:[Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"Do you want to begin with the QUIZ ?"}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){o(!0)},children:"START"})]})})})},x={quiz:[{question:"Where is Taj Mahal Located?",choices:["Mumbai","Agra","New Delhi","None of these"],correct:2},{question:"What color does yellow and green make?",choices:["Lime","Ocean mist","Maroon","Tangerine"],correct:1},{question:"The hottest planet in the solar system?",choices:["Mercury","Venus","Mars","Jupiter"],correct:1},{question:"'www' stands for:",choices:["World Wide Web","World Wide Wares","World Wide Wait","World Wide War"],correct:1},{question:"Which is the first smart city in world?",choices:["New Jersey","Seoul","Vatican City","California"],correct:2},{question:"Where is Gateway of India Located?",choices:["Mumbai","Chennai","New Delhi","Hyderabad"],correct:1},{question:"Which one of the following ports is the oldest port in India?",choices:["Mumbai Port","Chennai Port","Kolkata Port","Vishakhapatnam Port"],correct:2},{question:"Which is the tallest waterfalls in the world ?",choices:["Jog Falls","Tugela Falls","Angel Falls","Victoria Falls"],correct:3},{question:"Which of the following is called 'the Land of Rising Sun' ?",choices:["India","China","U.S.A","Japan"],correct:4},{question:"Which is the southernmost point of India?",choices:["Siachin","Indira Point","Thiruvananthapuram","Kanyakumari"],correct:2},{question:"For which of the following disciplines is Nobel Prize awarded?",choices:["Literature, Peace and Economics","Physics and Chemistry","Physiology or Medicine","All of the above"],correct:4},{question:"The United Nations Organization has its Headquarters at ",choices:["Bali","Hague","New York, USA","Washington DC"],correct:3},{question:" Objects at the surface of water can be viewed from a submarine under water by using which instrument ?",choices:["Stethescope","Periscope","Kaleidoscope","Telescope"],correct:2},{question:"Who created the famous Rock Garden of Chandigarh ?",choices:["Gaudi","Saarinen","Krishnarao Jaisim","Nek Chand"],correct:4},{question:"NASA\u2019s most famous space telescope goes by the name?",choices:["Muble Satellite Telescope"," Hubble Space Telescope","Humble Space Telescope","Galaxy Satellite Telescope"],correct:2},{question:"At room temperature, which is the only metal that is in liquid form?",choices:["Iron","Aluminum","Mercury","Silver"],correct:3},{question:"The tropic of cancer does not pass through which of these Indian states ?",choices:["Madhya Pradesh","West Bengal","Rajasthan","Odisha"],correct:4},{question:"In which of the following festivals are boat races a special feature?",choices:["Rongali Bihu ","Onam","Pongal","Navratri"],correct:2},{question:"The blue colour of the clear sky is due to",choices:["Diffraction of light","Dispersion of light","Reflection of light","Refraction of light"],correct:2}]},v=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:x;return e},w=Object(s.a)(v),_=Object(u.jsx)(a.a,{store:w,children:Object(u.jsx)(g,{})});n.a.render(_,document.getElementById("root"))},6:function(e,t,i){e.exports={App:"App_App__16ZpL",Container:"App_Container__10KOh",Content:"App_Content__ZaMNr"}}},[[23,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.a1da6366.chunk.js.map